<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Spaceshooter Zero</string>
    <string name="changePlayerName">Change player name</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="menuText">A game created by Anders, Jonas, Josef and Simon at Chalmers Uni.</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="globalHighscore">Global Highscore</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="highScore">High score</string>
    <string name="resetHighScore">Reset Highscores</string>
    <string name="resetSettings">Reset settings</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">""Welcome to an adventure like nothing else. Fly through the depths of space in the hunt for the answer to life, the universe and everything. We are sure that your findings will make you speachless."</string>
    <string name="help_message">"Weapons\nWhen starting the game, select one of the weapons showing (you might see more by scrolling the list using your finger to swipe up and down). Different weapons suit different players and ways of playing good or bad. Find your favourite by trying them all and by alternating your aggressiveness in the game.\n\nDamage\nHow much damage every projectile is dealing to an enemy. A higher number is better.\n\nReload\nThe time between each fired projectile. A lower number is better.\n\nSpread\nDefines how much the projectile deviates from the path of the ship. A higher number indicates a bigger spread.\n\nSpeed\nShows how fast the projectiles travels. A higher number indicates a faster projectile.\n\nSteering\nUse the green joystick on in the lower left corner of the game to steer the ship. The direction the joystick is dragged, the ship will start travelling to.\n\nHealth\nThe health bar is shown in the upper left corner of the game. You lose health by taking hits from enemies projectiles and by hitting smaller asteroids. Collisions with enemy ships or bigger asteroids leads to instant death.\n\nPower-ups\nIn the lower right corner of the game you'll see your inventory with saved power ups. Tap one of these to activate it's function.\n\nHealth pack\nThe read dots with a whit plus sign in them are health packs. Use these if you are low on health to be able to take more hits. If your health is full when picking up a health pack, it will be added to an empty inventory slot if you have one.\n\nSlow time\nThe blue dot with a hour glass on it slows down the time of everything else but your ship and your projectiles for a moment so that you can spend some time on killing more enemies.\n\nScore\nThe score is shown right under the health bar in the upper left corner of the game. Shooting enemies and asteroids gives you a certain number of points. If you manage to shoot many things in a short period of time, you will get a combo multiplier which can increase your score greatly."</string>
    <string name="sharedpreference_settings_key">com.spaceshooter.game.preferences.private.settings</string>
    <string name="sharedpreference_score_key">com.spaceshooter.game.preferences.private.scores</string>
    <string name="restartApp">Restart app</string>
    <string name="sharedpreferences_default_player_name">NeumanNobody</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="scores">Scores</string>
    <string name="names">Names</string>
    <string name="player">Player</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>

</resources>